picplz.com 2012-08-02

# picplz privacy policy

Last Updated: May 4, 2010

This Privacy Policy describes how picplz (“ **picplz** ,” “We,” “ **Us** ,” or “ **Our** ”) protects your privacy when you use picplz (the “ **Service** ”) which includes the Web site located at www.picplz.com (the “ **Site** ”) and all picplz mobile phone applications (“ **Mobile** ”).

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS DESCRIBED HEREIN AND ALL TERMS AND CONDITIONS INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH BELOW, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SERVICE. 

This Privacy Policy applies to information (including, personal information) collected through the Service. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “personal information” means information that identifies you personally, either alone or in combination with other information available to us. Personal information does not include "aggregate" information, which is data we collect about the use of the Service or about a group or category of services or users, from which individual identities or other personal information has been removed. This Privacy Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information, and we may share aggregate data about our users with third parties for various purposes. This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated into picplz’s [Terms of Service](http://www.picplz.com/terms) (“ **Terms of Service** ”). 

### The What & How of Information We Collect

Personal information may be collected in a number of ways. We may collect certain information that you voluntarily provide to us which may contain personal information. For example, we may collect your name, email address, user name, social network information and other information you provide us when you register, set up an account, contact us by e-mail or use our services. We may also obtain information from other companies and combine that with information we collect on the Service. When you visit the Site, some information may be automatically collected. For example, it is standard for your Web browser to automatically send information to every Web site you visit including ours. Such information includes your computer’s Internet Protocol (“ **IP** ”) address, access times, browser type and language, and referring Web site addresses. We may also collect information about your computer’s operating system and information about your usage and activity on the Site. 

_Cookies_ – We may automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small data files that are stored on your hard drive by a Web site. Among other things, the use of cookies helps us to improve the Site and your experience on the Site. We use cookies to see which areas and features of the Site are most popular, to count the number of computers accessing the Site, to personalize your experience and to remember your preferences. If your browser is set not to accept cookies or if you reject a cookie, you may not be able to access certain features or services of the Site.

 _Web Beacons_ – Web beacons, also known as gifs, are electronic images that may be used on the Site or in our emails. A Web beacon may be used on our Web pages to collect information, deliver cookies, count visits, compile statistics on usage and campaign effectiveness and in our emails to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

### Storage of Information & Transfer of Data

Most of the information we collect is retained by us on our servers. If you are using the Service from a country other than the country in which our Web servers are located (currently the United States of America) the various communications will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting the Site and communicating electronically with us, you consent to the processing and transfer of your data as set out in this Privacy Policy. 

### How We Use Your Personal Information

We use the information collected through the Service: (i) to communicate with you or third parties; (ii) to process your requests and transactions; (iii) to improve the Service; (iv) to customize the services and/or products we provide to you; (v) to assist with our product and service development; (vi) to perform marketing analysis; and (vii) for other purposes related to our business. 

### With Whom We Share Your Personal Information

Personal information collected through the Service may be shared with companies and organizations that perform services on our behalf (for example, companies that provide data management or other support services to us (such as data storage and Web hosting services)). Also, we may disclose the personal information we collect through the Service when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to: (i) comply with applicable law (or a court order or subpoena); (ii) prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; (iii) enforce the Terms of Service or other agreements that govern your use of the Service and/or our services; (iv) to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users or others; or (v) to protect your vital interests. Personal information submitted to the Service or collected by us is our asset and will become part of our normal business records. Your personal information and other data collected by us may be transferred to another company that has acquired our stock or assets, for example, as a result of a sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or liquidation. If such a transfer occurs, the acquiring company’s use of your personal information will still be subject to this Privacy Policy. 

### Modifying Your Information – Opt-Out / Opt-In

We respect your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose your personal information. You may update or modify your information or change your privacy preferences at any time by emailing us at privacy@picplz.com or, in some instances, via the Service. You may "opt-out" of receiving promotional communications including, but not limited to, promotional emails, from us by emailing us at privacy@picplz.com. Transactional service communications including, but not limited to, messages about your registration, will not be subject to the foregoing opt-out procedures. 

### SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We take reasonable security measures to protect your personal information (including, preventing the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction of your personal information). Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are impenetrable. If you use a password on the Service, you are responsible for keeping it confidential. Do not share it with any other person. If you believe your password has been misused, please advise us immediately. 

### MINORS

THIS SERVICE IS NOT MEANT FOR MINORS. We are committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. The Service is not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and we do not target the Service to children under 13. 

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may change this Privacy Policy from time-to-time. If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date above. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you visit the Service to understand how your personal information is used. 

### QUESTIONS

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please visit our query page at [picplz help](http://help.picplz.com/).
